My Husband's Double Life is a drama, mystery, tv
movie film directed by Alan Metzger.
A woman discovers that her husband faked his death and assumed a new
identity, while she struggled for 10 years as a single mother.
Elizabeth 'Peachy' Welsh, played by Margaret Colin.
Patrick Hennessy Welsh, played by Jay O. Sanders.
Chris Welsh, played by Aaron Ashmore.
Young Ted Welsh, played by Michael Cera.
Young Chris Welsh, played by Erik Knudsen.
Timothy Michael Kingsbury, played by Jay O. Sanders.
Double Indemnity is a 1944 American film noir directed by Billy
Wilder and produced by Buddy DeSylva and Joseph Sistrom.
Wilder and Raymond Chandler adapted the screenplay from James M.
Cain's novel of the same name, which ran as an
eight-part serial in Liberty magazine in 1936.
The film stars an insurance salesman Walter Neff (Fred MacMurray), who plots with a woman (Barbara Stanwyck) to kill her
husband in order to claim a life insurance payment, arousing the suspicion of claims manager Barton Keyes (Edward G.
The title refers to a "double indemnity" clause which doubles life insurance
payouts when death occurs in a statistically rare manner.
The film was nominated for seven Academy Awards.
Widely regarded as a classic, Double Indemnity is often cited as having set the
standard for film noir and as one of the greatest films of all time.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.